

Giulia Florentina Apostolescu

Details

Cluj-Napoca Romania 0758331494

giulia.apostolescu@gmail.com

DRIVING LICENSE

В

DATE OF BIRTH

18.04.1998

Skills

Adaptability

Fast Learner

Ability to Multitask

Customer Service

Ability to Work Under Pressure

Ability to Work in a Team

Languages

English

Profile

As a teenage, I developed skills based on my activity as a professional volleyball player. After high school, I worked for four months in two different companies, so that I could pay the first tax for the college that I applied. Since I started college, I tried to focus on volunteering a little more, so I applied to UBB students organization, where at this time I am an active member of the HR department, and also member of the general assembly, witch means that along other members, we talk about most of the important decisions for our organization. Also, I graduated Bachelor Degree at "Babeṣ-Bolyai" University, degree in political science, more exactly, I am specialized in security studies, and did my bachelor degree on the subject of Human Security in Public Health.

Employment History

Operator, Grs, Piatra Neamţ

FEBRUARY 2018 - APRIL 2018

Sales assistant, Inditex, Piatra Neamţ

JUNE 2018 - JULY 2018

Cashier, TIFF, Cluj-Napoca

MAY 2019 - JUNE 2019

Cashier, Neversea, Constanța

JULY 2019 - JULY 2018

Cashier, Untold, Cluj-Napoca

AUGUST 2019 - AUGUST 2019

Key Account Manager, Extreme Structure, Cluj-Napoca

FEBRUARY 2021 - PRESENT

Education

"Octav Onicescu" National High School, Bucharest

SEPTEMBER 2013 - JUNE 2017

Security studies, Babes-Bolyai University of Cluj-Napoca, Cluj-Napoca

OCTOBER 2018 - JULY 2021

Extra-curricular activities

Proffesional Volleyball Player, LPS Piatra Neamt, Piatra Neamţ

JULY 2008 - JULY 2012

Proffesional Volleyball Player, CSM Bucharest, Bucharest

AUGUST 2012 - AUGUST 2016

Volunteer, UBB Centenary Activities

OCTOBER 2019 - OCTOBER 2019

Volunteer, OSUBB, Cluj-Napoca

OCTOBER 2019 - PRESENT

Volunteer, UBB Goes Green, Cluj-Napoca

NOVEMBER 2019 - NOVEMBER 2019

College coordinator, Junior Summer University